Contact

+923044662975 (Home) saadmehmood096@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/saadmehmood-a2aa6917a (LinkedIn) www.fiverr.com/saadmehmood609 (Personal)

Top Skills

Search Engine Marketing (SEM)
Sales & Marketing
WordPress

Saad Mehmood

Digital Marketing Consultant | SMM | SEO Expert

Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

Summary

Hi! I'm Saad, I'm a professional Digital Marketing Expert from last 6 years.

My core skills are:

- -Search Engine Optimization(SEO)
- -Social Media Marketing(SMM)
- -Social media optimization(SMO)
- -Search engine marketing(SEM)
- -(WordPress) (Weebly) (Wix) (webflow)
- -SEO Content Writing
- -Facebook & Instagram Ads
- -Google Ads
- -Shopify
- -WordPress

I have helped many local businesses significantly improve their Google rankings and traffic. Joined this platform to gain more exposure with wonderful clients like you. I'm ready to help your business to skyrocket your organic traffic.

Experience

Upwork

UPWORK - DIGITAL MARKETING EXPERT

June 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Chicago Office. 525 W. Van Buren. Suite 1100. Chicago. IL 60607.

Hi! I'm Saad, I'm a professional Search Engine Optimization specialist with over 6 years of experience in Digital Marketing.

Fiverr

6 years

Search Engine Optimization Specialist

February 2017 - Present (6 years)

Pakistan

Digital Marketing Specialist November 2017 - January 2023 (5 years 3 months)

Pakistan

Education

Superior College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (March 2017 - January 2021)